nationstates2.com 2009-06-16

# 

**Privacy Policy**

You are using a website which is owned or operated by OMAC Industries (www.omacindustries.com). OMAC Industries has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for www.omacindustries.com and other Internet properties owned or operated by OMAC Global Media Limited including but not limited to www.nationstates.net, www.nationstates2.com, www.jolt.co.uk, www.swirve.com and www.trukz.com.

**Information Collected**

In general, you can visit our websites without providing personal information, but there are times when we will request personal information (such as a valid email address), usually in order to play one of our online games. In some situations, you may also be required to provide personal information in order to make a purchase within a specific game. You may not provide false registration information about yourself. If you do provide us with any information, it WILL NOT BE SHARED with any other company. Any information you receive will ALWAYS come from us (either an omacindustries.com address or one of our subsidiaries).

This next part sounds a little menacing but it's really not so please don't freak out, it's completely normal for any website. We may also track your visit to our site by giving you a "cookie" when you enter. Cookies are pieces of information that websites transfer to your computer's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. OMAC Industries uses cookies to make visiting our sites easier. Information collected through the use of cookies is also used to evaluate and improve our websites and to help diagnose problems with our servers. Cookies allow us to save passwords and preferences for you so that you won't have to re-enter them the next time you visit. Cookies help us to collect anonymous click-stream data for tracking user trends and patterns. The use of cookies is now an industry standard, and you'll find them used on most major websites. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you prefer, you can reset your browser either to notify you when you've received a cookie or to refuse to accept cookies. You should understand that areas of certain sites will not function properly if you set your browser not to accept cookies.

**How We Use the Information**

We collect and use your information in order to give you better service, to provide you with convenient access to our products and services and to make our websites more useful to you. The contact information we collect is used to process account queries, deliver game-specific news and alerts and relevant promotional material. It is also used to contact you when necessary. OMAC Industries is a global company with operations throughout the world. When you submit personal information to OMAC Industries through its website, you agree that your information may be transferred across national boundaries and may be stored and processed in any of the countries in which OMAC Industries and/or its affiliates are located.

**Public Forums**

Our site makes extensive use of forums and message boards available to its users. Please remember that any information disclosed in these areas is public information and can be accessed through any search engine. Please, please, please don't post personal or financial information here. OMAC Industries is not responsible for the content or protection of any information disclosed in these areas, or anything that might happen as a result. Seriously, please be sensible with your data.

**Choice/Opt-Out**

When you provide us with your contact information, you may opt-out of receiving communications from us at any time by sending an email with your name and email address to info [at] omacindustries.com, with the subject line, REMOVE.

**Privacy of Other Sites**

OMAC Industries' websites may contain links to other sites whose privacy and information practices may be different than ours. We do our very best to only partner with companies and communities who are professionally run and respect their users but ultimately we can't control how they treat your data. You should make a point of consulting the other sites' privacy notices. Just so we're clear: OMAC Industries is not responsible for the content or privacy policies of other sites that we don't own or operate.

**Security**

We use physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to help safeguard the information we collect from you online. We urge you to take precautions to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. Change your passwords often and make sure you use a secure browser. Also, don't use your email password as your game password.

**Correcting Information/ Contacting the Web Site**

If you wish to correct any information you have provided to us or if you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with our websites, you can contact info [at] omacindustries.com.

This privacy policy is subject to change without notice. Last edited July 25th 2008
